Deliver them from evil.
Deathwatch is a drama, horror, thriller film directed by MJ Bassett.
In the brutal trench fighting of the First World War, a British Infantry
Company is separated from their regiment after a fierce battle.
Attempting to return to their lines, the British soldiers discover what appears to be a
bombed out German trench, abandoned except for a few dazed German soldiers.
After killing most of the Germans, and taking one prisoner, the British company
fortifies to hold the trench until reinforcements can arrive.
Soon, however, strange things being to happen as a sense of evil descends
on the trench and the British begin turn on each other.
Pfc. Charlie Shakespeare, played by Jamie Bell.
Pvt. Colin Chevasse, played by Rúaidhrí Conroy.
Martin Plummer, played by Mike Downey.
Capt. Bramwell Jennings, played by Laurence Fox.
German soldier, played by Roman Horák.
Pvt. Willie McNess, played by Dean Lennox Kelly.
Deathwatch is a 2002 horror war film set during
World War I, written and directed by M.
Bassett, and starring Jamie Bell, Laurence Fox, Kris
Marshall, Matthew Rhys and Andy Serkis.
It follows a lost squad of British soldiers who take refuge in an enemy trench,
only to discover it is haunted by a malevolent supernatural force.
The film explores themes of supernatural, assault,
soldier, trenches, horrors of war.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.